Aron Moelich (Mr.)

Date of birth: 10/04/1988

Nationality: Citizenship: South African . Permanent Resident in: Ireland (Stamp 4)

Address: Knappaghmore, Sligo Town F91 PW08, Ireland

Phone number: +353 (0)87 716 4114 Email address: aron.moelich88@gmail.com



Profile

I am a dilligent and self-driven employee with experience working as a team member in various strict and professional settings. I pride myself in being focussed and hard-working towards any job at hand, while conveying a positive attitude towards those around me. I am currently fully dedicated in persuing a career in software development and geared towards life-long learning within the profession.

Education

06/2014 - 06/2017 PRETORIA, SOUTH AFRICA

Development Studies & Sociology | Bachelors of Arts University of South Africa (UNISA)

(NFQ Level 7) - Majoring in Sociology and Development

Studies at the University of South Africa

07/2022 - 07/2023 DUBLIN, IRELAND

Full Stack Software Development | Diploma

Code Institute, Dublin

Diploma (NFQ Level 5) in full stack software development. HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Bootstrap, Django, React.

Skills

~ SOFTWARE LANGUAGES

HTML Proficient

CSS Skilled - Moderate
JavaScript Entry Level- Ongoing
Python Entry Level- Ongoing

~ SOFTWARE FRAMEWORKS

Bootstrap Skilled - Moderate
React Limited - Ongoing
JQuery Limited - Ongoing

Work Experience

04/2013 - 08/2017 OFFSHORE,

THAILAND, INDONESIA, MALDIVES, MALAYSIA

Coastal Skipper/Sailor Independent Sailing

Junior Skipper/First Mate delivering sailing vessels to and from multiple South East Asian countries. Private contracting. Working in and with small crews on long distance voyages transporting and maintenancing large sailing vessels.

- coordinated the movements of a vessel and its crew
- oversaw the vessel's journey.
- maintained control, ensured safety of the vessel and its crew.

07/2017 - 12/2019 CHACHOENGSAO, THAILAND

English Teacher Wat Don Tong School, Thailand

Full-time English Teacher, Wat Don Thong Primary School, Thailand. English conversation, listening and speaking as an ESL teacher.

- Led classroom discussions.
- Wrote and developed lesson plans.
- Taught English grammar, composition, and literature.

03/2020 - PRESENT SLIGO, IRELAND

Supervisor/site manager Coney Island Shellfish .Ltd

Aquaculture/Farming of various shellfish such as oysters, mussels and clams. Responsible for management of farm and completion of daily tasks.

- Trained new employees on company procedures.
- Created work schedules
- Enforced safety regulations

☆ Strengths

- # Adaptable # Self-Driven # Responsible
- # Mature Student # Fast Learner
- # Native English Speaker # Licensed Driver